

# Maxim Reksha

#### Contact

Reksha

Dereh Namir 107

**Phone** 

0545502916

**Email** 

mreksha@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/maxim-reksha/

#### Site

https://maximilianix.github.io/portfolio-site/

## **Additional Skills**

Front:

HTML,CSS,JS(es6+),XML,SASS Back: PHP,AJAX,REST Services, MySQL Frameworks: ReactJS, Redux, iQuery, Bootstrap, GULP

jQuery, Bootstrap, GULP Other: GIT, Jira, Agile workflow, NPM, Responsive design, Cross Browser compatibility

# **Professional Summary**

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with over 5 years of front-end experience and 3+ in back-end, designing, developing, managing responsive sites and internal frameworks with "mobile-first" approach. A fast learner with good coding skills, analytical thinking, attention to details, patience, accuracy, and time management. Have excellent communication skills as well as professional ethics.

## Work Experience

2019 - 2020

#### **FullStack Developer - Webpals**

- Developing, building, and maintaining WordPress first tier sites using React.
- Creating widgets and plugins based on PHP,MYSQL,Reactjs and responsive front-end.
- Agile workflow with a team.

2017 - 2019

## FullStack Web Developer - 888 Holdings

- Translated design team's UX mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/CSS/JavaScript and AJAX, JSON with jQuery.
- Executed and contributed to full-stack web development projects, with an emphasis on front end features, browser manipulation, and cross-browser compatibility.
- Assisted in development of back end features in PHP.
- Troubleshooted issues affecting production, stage, and development environments as requested.

2015 - 2017

## Webmaster & PHP Developer - IGMD Itd

- Building fully responsive, cross browser websites.
- Work with an established team of developers and interact with product managers, marketing teams and designers.
- Develop features for CRM using AJAX, PHP, MySql database.
- · Working with Restful API's.

#### Education

2014-2015

#### Web development and SEO course - HAckerU

Three Years of studying

2008-2011

#### **Economic & Business administration - Ariel University**

#### Languages

English — C1 - Advanced

Russina — C2 - Proficient